{
    "data": {
        "title": "Realtor Flashcards",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "Zoning laws",
                "hint": "Police",
                "answer": "Police = enact"
            },
            {
                "question": "Open-end Clause",
                "hint": "need more money",
                "answer": "Allows borrower to increase their loans"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are zoning laws?",
                "hint": "land",
                "answer": "Controls what can be developed on a land and what you can do with it."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the purpose of tax shelter?",
                "hint": "save money",
                "answer": "reduces tax liability"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the main purpose for zoning ordinances?",
                "hint": "who does it protect?",
                "answer": "Homeowner protection"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is zoning ordinances?",
                "hint": "a rule",
                "answer": "A rule that defines how property in specific geographic zones can be used. Whether for residential or commercial."
            },
            {
                "question": "Density means?",
                "hint": "A measurement",
                "answer": "A measurement of land per acre"
            },
            {
                "question": "What does portability mean?",
                "hint": "transferable",
                "answer": "Can take the benefits with them to the new home within 24 months."
            },
            {
                "question": "what is an IRS 1031 exchange?",
                "hint": "Trading",
                "answer": "a swap of one investment property for another that allows capital gains tax to be deferred."
            },
            {
                "question": "what's all debt, including accounts and notes that are payable, known as?",
                "hint": "debt",
                "answer": " Liabilities"
            },
            {
                "question": "Asset",
                "hint": "resources",
                "answer": "Entire resources including tangible and intangible"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is dedication?",
                "hint": "land no longer private",
                "answer": "Giving up private land for public use."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is another term for farming?",
                "hint": "think business",
                "answer": "the practice of concentrating business efforts in a particular geographical area"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is a home built from blueprints supplied by the buyer called?",
                "hint": "A home your way",
                "answer": "A custom home"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is NOT the term for farming?",
                "hint": "Another term for farming but not in regards to business",
                "answer": "involves raising crops, fish, or animals"
            },
            {
                "question": "What's an organization with at least one real estate broker acting as the agent for others in negotiating the sale or rental of real property for a fee called?",
                "hint": "organization for sales ",
                "answer": "A real estate brokerage"

            },
            {
                "question": "Who can complete an appraisal?",
                "hint": "a person who specializes in appraisals",
                "answer": "A licensed appraiser using USPAP standards"
            } ,
            {
                "question": "What does the acronym MLS stand for?",
                "hint": "think a system",
                "answer": "Multiple Listing System"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is not considered a major real estate licensee sales specialty?",
                "hint": "not",
                "answer": "Cemetery Plots"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is considered a major real estate licensee sales specialty?",
                "hint": "homes",
                "answer": "Residential"
            },

            {
                "question": "What's considered personal property?",
                "hint": "not real",
                "answer": "Any property which is not real property."
            },            
            {
                "question": "What's a proprietary Lease?",
                "hint": "Used in a co-op context",
                "answer": "A lease given by a corporation to another that provides the share owner with the right to live in a particular unit or apartment."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is a prospectus?",
                "hint": "Used for condominium development",
                "answer": "A document that summarizes some of the major points contained in the condominium documents."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who prepares the prospectus?",
                "hint": "a developer that's developed a certain amount of condominium",
                "answer": " A developer of 20 or more condominium units."
            },
            {
                "question": "What type of lease is used in co-ops?",
                "hint": "It's given from one corporation to another",
                "answer": "A Proprietary Lease."
            },
            {
                "question": "What document does a developer need after building more than 20 condominium units?",
                "hint": "This document summarizes the condominium documents",
                "answer": "a prospectus"
            },
            {
                "question": "What's considered real estate?",
                "hint": "soil",
                "answer": "Land plus anything permanently attached to land"
            },
            {
                "question": "What's real Property?",
                "hint": "soil, etc",
                "answer": "Land, things affixed to land, appurtenances, plus the bundle of rights."
            },
            {
                "question": "Remainderman is known as...",
                "hint": "inheritance or entitlement",
                "answer": "A person who inherits or is entitled to inherit property upon the termination of the estate of the former owner."
            },
            {
                "question": "what is the Right of Survivorship?",
                "hint": "The distinguishing feature of a joint tenancy.",
                "answer": "The right of a surviving tenant or tenants to succeed to the entire interest of the deceased tenant."
            },
            {
                "question": "The distinguishing feature of a joint tenancy is known as",
                "hint": "The rights of a surviving tenant(s) to succeed to the entire interest of the deceased tenant",
                "answer": "The Right of Survivorship."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the beneficial interests associated with real property?",
                "hint": "There are 5 rights",
                "answer": "Possession, Enjoyment, Disposition, Control and Exclusion."
            },
            {
                "question": "Separate Property Rights",
                "hint": "The distinguishing feature of a joint tenancy.",
                "answer": "Are rights that can be sold separately like, possession, enjoyment, disposition, controls and exclusion."
            },
            {
                "question": "what's a tenancy at sufferance?",
                "hint": "A temporary visa has expired or overstaying your welcome",
                "answer": "An estate lawfully acquired for a temporary period of time but retained after a period of lawful possession has expired."
            },
            {
                "question": "An estate that may be terminated by either party at any time with proper notice is known as...",
                "hint": "an open lease",
                "answer": "Tenancy at will"
            },
            {
                "question": "what is a tenancy by Entireties?",
                "hint": "The distinguishing feature of a joint tenancy.",
                "answer": "A tenancy created by a husband and wife jointly owning real property with an automatic and complete right of survivorship."
            },
            {
                "question": "what is Tenancy in Common?",
                "hint": "interests are not passed to surviving tenants",
                "answer": "A form of ownership by two or more persons each having an equal or unequal interest and passing the interest to heirs."
            },
            {
                "question": "Time-share",
                "hint": "evil",
                "answer": "A form of subdivision of real property into rights to the recurrent exclusive use or occupancy of a lot, parcel, unit or segment of real property, on an annual or some other periodic basis for a specified period of time."
            }
        ]
    }
}